winsite.com 2002-12-05

# Welcome to WinSite! The place for shareware, demoware, trialware, tips, and utilities for your computer

WinSite Privacy Statement

Welcome to WinSite, **The Planet's Largest Software Archive for Windows shareware and trialware on the Internet**. WinSite Group (formerly the CICA Windows FTP archives)

**Third Party** **Advertising.** WinSite has partnered with [MAXWORLDWIDE](http://www.maxworldwide.com/) (formerly known as L90), who serves ads for us. To learn more, please visit [them](http://www.maxworldwide.com/). 

We use MaxWorldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)  

**Third Party Cookies.** In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.  

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this industry-standard information by WinSite Group, Inc. If changes are made to this privacy policy, they will be posted here, so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Security**. Any and all information that WinSite collects on its visitors is securely stored and is removed from the system each month to off-disk storage. We use additional security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use Secure Shell to access our servers remotely, and all server sessions are encrypted.

**Privacy.** WinSite cares about your privacy. As with most industry-standard web serving software, each visit to our website generates a logfile entry that indicates time of visit, the domain name of your machine (e.g., "dial-54.somewhere.com") and the file(s) (and their sizes, in bytes) that your visit generated.

WinSite uses information generated from each visitor to our website to determine popular downloads and the most often-used sections of our website. **WinSite does not collect personal information.** We use industry standard web server logfiles to record baseline visitor information. **WinSite does not sell, trade, or rent any visitor information**. The data we collect is for internal use only and for the use of reporting to our advertisers the number of advertising impressions we deliver. 

**Lastly, a word or two about e-mail.** As one of the busiest and most popular sites on the Internet, we open ourselves to the nefarious exploits of some of the more unscrupulous activities of spammers, bulk and mass e-mailers, and their ilk. We have taken great measures to secure our file servers from their **constant** attack(s) that try to use our precious resources to relay thousands of unsolicited e-mail messages. We are proud participants of the [Mail Abuse Prevention System (MAPS)](http://www.mail-abuse.org/). MAPS is a California nonprofit company whose goal is to stop the Internet's e-mail system from being abused by spammers. MAPS principal means of doing this is by educating and encouraging ISPs and content providers such as WinSite, to enforce strong terms and conditions prohibiting abusive e-mail practices. We agressively use the [MAPS Relay Spam Stopper](http://www.mail-abuse.org/rss/). WinSite does not sell mail service(s). We don't sell Internet access. We do not send mass e-mail. **We do not "do" spam.** In fact, we loathe spam and those who generate it. You have our word that you will **never** receive unsolicited e-mail from us. Ever. If you hate spam as much as we do, and want to learn more about spam and how to deal with it, please visit the wonderful anti-spam web site at [http://spam.abuse.net](http://spam.abuse.net/). You'll find everything there that you need to put an end to spam once and for all!

We provide this statement as an assurance to you. We want you to know that your privacy is respected and will not be abused or violated by visiting our site. We also hope that by providing this privacy statement, other sites will join us in reaffirming your rights of privacy while using the Internet.

**We welcome your input!  
**Please let us know what you think about our privacy statement. Your comments are always welcome at our[Contact](http://www.winsite.com/cgi-bin/contact) page.

Last updated: Tue Oct 22 22:33:28 2002
